## Sandra Krle

Visby, Sweden ↑
sandra.krlle@gmail.com ✓
www.linkedin.com/in/sandrakrle in

A self-taught frontend developer with 2 years of work experience with focus on React. Looking for a caring organization with time and dedication to the development of their employees. Fast pace and new things to learn are my motivation drivers.

### **Skills**

Development:

- HTML/CSS
- LESS/SCSS
- JavaScript
- JQuery, Angular, React
- Redux
- Node.js

### Testing:

- Karma, Mocha, Chai
- Webdriver.io
- Enzyme

#### Helpers:

- Chrome dev tools
- Git
- Npm
- Webstorm
- Jira
- Jenkins CI

## **Experience**

2017 MARCH - CURRENT

# CMS Frontend developer @ www.svenskaspel.se Visby, Sweden

#### The national gambling company of Sweden

Working on developing and maintaining an internal CMS web application used to manage the content for the Svenska Spel's web site and game products.

I am one of three frontend developers in a team of eight persons including backend, UI/UX and a Product Owner.

The frontend stack is React+Redux+Node.

My tasks include developing new features (e.g. new types of widgets, banners, time scheduling tools for the content, A/B testing options)

Maintenance of existing features (bug fixing, rewriting legacy code from Backbone to React, performance optimization, updating of tests)

Writing unit tests with Enzyme, functional (UI) and integration (API) tests with Mocha and webdriver.io.

JAN 2017 - FEB 2017

# Frontend developer - consultant @ www.competencer.com Stockholm, Sweden

#### Web app for online consultations with health advisers

Developed a feature for an online psychological stress test in Angular <a href="https://www.competencer.com/stress">www.competencer.com/stress</a> test

SEP 2017 - DEC 2017

## Frontend developer @ www.edqu.se Stockholm, Sweden

#### Online classroom

Worked on developing and maintenance of features of the web app. Was working under the mentorship of a senior developer from whom I learned a lot about Angular and UX. I also helped with the creating of their app's style guide.

MARCH 2017 - JUL 2017

## Frontend developer - intern @ www.fundedbyme.com Stockholm, Sweden

#### Online platform for crowdfunding

My first internship as a Frontend developer. Started with the basics, some HTML and CSS and later focused more on JavaScript. I mainly worked on improving already existing features and some bug fixes.

2010 - 2014

### Financial Analyst Skopje, Macedonia

Before moving to Sweden I worked In Macedonia as an accountant and analyst for financial companies.

## **Education**

NOV 2015 - MARCH 2017

### Online courses in Frontend

Coursera, Codecademy, Free Code Camp and few others were my intro to Frontend development.

# **Bachelor of Financial Management / State university** of Macedonia, Cyril and Methodius

## About me

I have 32 years and live in Visby, Sweden.

I am originally from Macedonia, but moved to Sweden with my husband who was offered a job opportunity in Stockholm.

I have been living in Stockholm from 2014 till 2017 and then moved to Visby where I was employed at one of Sweden's most famous company Svenska Spel.

Although I have a formal education and work experience in the field of finance, I was never truly happy in that position and have always dreamed about going into IT. With the move to Sweden I got the fresh start I was looking for. It's been a steep learning curve but I believe the progress I made in such a short time speaks highly of my fast learning abilities and motivation to become a great developer.

I chose frontend because it combines my aesthetic sense for visual design and my analytical mind. I have always dabbled in Photoshop creating designs or retouching images for friends. Working with frontend allows me to have a say in the design as well. I try to make each feature pixel perfect.

Beside my interest in the latest developments in the frontend world, in my free time I love to explore the beautiful Swedish nature. I am an avid music listener and recently became a proud owner of a vinyl record player.

I am outgoing and an easy-to-talk to person. I love meeting new people from all over the world and to share our expat experience and survival tips.